These days, the only AI content that
performs well on YouTube that people
seem to care about is content on Claude.
Every new model, new feature that's
released, the latest plugin that's going
viral, everyone rushes to make that next
YouTube video. There are dozens of
creators now in this space that are
creating the same video every time we
have a new model or a new release. And
don't get me wrong, it's important to
track with all the latest AI news, but I
don't jive with just being a channel
that covers all that instead of real
engineering. That's what I want to give
to you. And so, I want to talk about
that a little bit today and just give
you a quick channel update as well,
because I want to do a lot more live
streaming now, showing you the real
systems and real engineering principles
of AI coding, not just the news. And so,
I'm going to start live streaming
Mondays, Thursdays, and Saturdays at
9:00 a.m. Central Time. I'm just going
to try this for a couple of weeks and
see if you like it. And so, I'm going to
be doing a lot of live building. I'll
talk about what that looks like. And
just for the next couple minutes here, I
want to share why I'm doing this shift.
And I've actually been live streaming a
lot more recently already, multiple per
week for the last few weeks, and I have
been loving it. It's such an awesome
format. And don't get me wrong, I still
like making normal YouTube videos. I'm
going to keep doing that once a week,
but I want to try this new cadence of
live streaming multiple times a week as
well. I've gotten really good at making
these streams interactive, answering all
your questions. It's just such a great
format to show you how I really use
Claude Code and these other coding
agents day-to-day, building all things
like Arkon and the Dark Factory. I'll
talk about all that in a little bit.
But, yeah, this just really jives with
my YouTube channel. If you search for
Claude or Claude Code, you're going to
just see so many of the exact same
video. And I don't want to actually do
the search right now cuz I don't want to
call out any specific creators. I really
do respect all the other AI content
creators in this space. I just don't
want to fall in that bucket. My channel
has always been a bit deeper, where I'm
covering, you know, the principles of
building your second brain to really
build AI agents and use coding
assistants in ways that actually scale.
I want to keep up with that, even though
the YouTube algorithm doesn't favor
those things as much right now. And it's
a big bummer for me, but I want to stick
to what I really want to teach and what
I think is the most fulfilling and
useful. And I still will cover the AI
news and the latest trends when I think
it's important. Like when Karpathy
releases LLM Wiki architecture, I
covered that. I covered Claude agent
teams when that was released. So, I'm
still covering some of the newest
features, and I want to do that a lot,
but the point is, I'm not going to rush
to make a video within 4 hours of that
thing being released. I'm going to
actually tinker with it, incorporate it
into my systems, and then it teach you
that. So, there's still a lot of
substance and educational value from my
content. So, a lot of that mixed with
the timeless principles that I've always
wanted to focus on. And these live
streams are going to allow me to keep
making some YouTube videos on the latest
trends in AI news while still giving you
a lot of substance every single week,
showing you how my AI coding process is
evolving over time, building Arkon live
with you. There's so much value that I
have planned for these streams. And one
more thing that I want to say on
covering all the latest news and trends,
one of the biggest reasons I don't want
to do that is because I don't see as
much value in those kinds of videos when
you can just ask your coding agent how
these new features work. Like especially
with Claude Code, what I want to show
you right here is that Claude has an
internal skill to search its own
documentation. So, when a new feature
comes out, like  by the way or
the memory system with the dreaming or
we have routines that were added
recently. Sure, these videos can be
helpful, and I'm not telling you to
never watch them, but a lot of what you
need you can get by simply asking Claude
Code how this new feature works, and it
has real-time access to up-to-date
documentation to give you summaries and
help you incorporate these ideas into
your own system, like your own agent
decoding workflows and your own second
brain. And so, that plus the fact that
every single YouTuber seems to be
covering the exact same thing means that
a majority of the videos that are coming
on on YouTube right now, you just don't
need to watch. And that's why I'm trying
to be set apart, continuing to show you
the more high-leverage skills, not just
new features. And I'm really not just
trying to say that my videos are better.
In fact, a lot of these guys and gals
have such polished videos for all the
new AI trends and news. It's pretty
awesome, and I would recommend, you
know, picking one or two to follow. But,
I'm just trying to explain why I want to
do something different, going more in
this direction of deeper live streams,
still keeping up a normal cadence for my
usual content. And so, for these live
streams, I want to chat about this now a
little bit. So, again, 9:00 a.m. Central
Time every Monday, Thursday, and
Saturday. A lot of different things that
I've been doing on my live streams,
especially I want to keep working on
Arkon live with you. So, this is my
open-source harness builder for AI
coding. I'll link to a video right here
where I give the introduction for it.
This is a huge passion project of mine.
I love building it live with you guys
and also evolving the vision with you.
So, a lot more of this. I've also been
working on my Dark Factory experiment,
which is a code base and I'm handing the
reins over completely to AI coding
assistants. No human is allowed to
review code or even write any code. And
so, working on these two things, a lot
of other applications that I want to
build with the help of Arkon, this is
what I have planned right now for my
live streams. They're going to be super
engaging. I want to just make sure that
it's always full of a ton of educational
value. So, that's what I got going on
for my channel right now. I don't have
one scheduled yet, but by the time this
video goes live, I will have my next
live stream ready for you to enable
notifications for. I'm going to do that
this Saturday the 9th at 9:00 a.m.
Central Time. So, I'm going to really
start my cadence here of Monday,
Thursdays, and Saturdays, starting this
Saturday the 9th. And every live stream
is going to be somewhere between an hour
and a half and 2 and a half hours. And
after the stream is done, the recording
automatically shows up on the live tab
here for my channel. you can't make it
to the live stream, you can still watch
it and sift through it like a regular
YouTube video if you would like. Plus, I
am thinking about creating some kind of
system where I can take these live
streams and split them out into more
polished videos to put on my channel.
So, the live stream is where you can
really see me build out my system in
real time, and then I'll take, you know,
the really good educational pieces, and
continue to put that out as regular
videos on my channel. We'll see what it
looks like. This is new to me, but it's
important for me to experiment here
because I want to make sure I'm giving
you the most value possible in the sea
of all of the Claude Code hype. So, if
you're sick of watching the same Claude
hype videos every single week, come join
me. Not that you have to ditch that
content entirely. I want to reiterate
that there is value there, but I just
hope that my content with its unique
value can make its way into what you
watch on a weekly basis with my
Wednesday videos and my live streams.
So, starting again with this Saturday
live stream the 9th at 9:00 a.m. Central
Time, the first one that I'm doing with
this really consistent schedule. I'm
going to be doing some live building
with Arkon, creating Arkon workflows to
make AI coding reliable and repeatable.
So, I hope to see you there. And also,
let me know in the comments if you're
looking forward to these live streams,
if you think it's a dumb idea. Of
course, I'd want to know that as well.
Let me know what you think. But, yeah,
I'd love to go on this journey with you
as I experiment with some new content
here, just trying to give you as much
value as possible. And so, if you
appreciated this quick little update and
you're looking forward to more live
streams and more building with Arkon and
AI coding, I would really appreciate a
like and a subscribe. And with that, I
will see you in the next video or live
stream.